Daniel Gawne

Front End Developer

Daniel Gawne

Lake Mary, FL 32746

danielgawne@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dgwne/

GitHub: https://github.com/dgwn

Skills

I have experience with HTML/CSS, vanilla JS, React, Git, Adobe Photoshop, and Adobe XD, as well as some exposure to Python, R, and Ruby. I am a self-taught programmer which I believe demonstrates my dedication to continued and self-directed learning.

Experience

Raterlabs, Inc. / Internet Analyst

JUNE 2017 - PRESENT, Remote

Conduct research, evaluation and feedback on search engine results by, but not limited to: measuring the relevance and usefulness of web pages in correlation to predefined queries, by providing comparative analysis of sets of search engine results and various other techniques. Evaluates and improves search engine results for some of the world's largest internet search engine companies.

Fleet Farming / Digital Media/Marketing Intern

JAN 2018 - MAY 2018, Orlando, FL

Developed targeted Facebook ad campaigns for selected demographics, wrote original ad copy, managed Facebook and Instagram feeds, calculated effectiveness of ad spending on sales and brand awareness, monitored Google Analytics for our website, monitored and selected keywords using Google AdWords, drafted and designed promotional materials for both print and web (e.g. fliers, calendar, infographics, and stickers), contacted printers/distributors for the above printed materials, and developed action plans for future interns in the Media/Marketing department.

Leapforce / Search Engine Evaluator

SEPT 2015 - MAY 2017. Remote

Conducted in depth internet-based research and provided information evaluation for leading search and social media companies from around the globe.

Education

University of Central Florida/ Philosophy B.A. (Sociology Minor)

2012 - 2017, Orlando, FL

Certifications

Responsive Web Design (FreeCodeCamp)

Javascript Algorithms & Data Structures (FreeCodeCamp)

Adobe Certified Associate (Photoshop CS5)